oil-price.net 2018-12-21

# Privacy Policy

< Back

Effective 2017/09/27 

At OIL-PRICE.NET, we collect and manage user data according to the following Privacy Policy. This document is part of OIL-PRICE.NET's Terms of Service, and by using OIL-PRICE.NET (the "Website"), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. Please read the Terms of Service in their entirety, and refer to those for definitions and contacts. 

### Data Collection

When you use our Services we may collect the content and other information you provide. This includes information used to create your account (e.g., a username, password and at your option, an email address) and account preferences. 

### Use of Data

We use the Personal Information we collect from and about you to process your registration. We also use aggregate information for the purpose of monitoring site traffic and to improve the quality of our products. 

We also use your information to deliver relevant online advertising. 

We may use your Personal Information as we believe to be necessary in order to defend, enforce or protect the legal rights of OIL-PRICE.NET or their employees or contractors, protect the security of users, protect against fraud, comply with the law or legal processes including outside your country of residence. 

### Use of cookies

We use cookies to maintain your language preferences and grant you access to features requiring logging in. You can set your browser to not accept cookies. However some of the website features will then not be available to you. 

### Ads and Analytics

We may partner with third-party ad networks and analytics providers to deliver relevant advertising. These third-parties may collect information sent to them by your browser in response to a request for content. OIL-PRICE.NET does not share your information or account details with advertisers. We cannot see advertisers' cookies and advertisers do not see OIL-PRICE.NET cookies. 

### Protecting your information

We will use reasonable efforts to safeguard your information but cannot guarantee the integrity of confidentiality of data transferred to you via the Internet as the Internet is not entirely secure. 

### Changes

OIL-PRICE.NET may modify this Privacy Policy. Any change will become effective when the revised Private Policy is posted; the effective date is listed at the top. Your use of OIL-PIRCE.NET following these changes means that your accept the revised policy. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, we ask that you email contact at oil-price.net. Please do not disclose any personal information when contacting us.
